

Alejandro Yunes Front-end Dev.

https://vanguardia.tech/alejandro

I am a passionate front-end developer with 5 years of professional experience, specializing in crafting web applications from the initial planning phase to the final deployment using React and its ecosystem. Throughout my career in web development, I have gained knowledge in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node, Express, GraphQL, MongoDB, and scrum methodology.

Professional Resume

Experience

2023 - present

Vanguardia.tech

FullStack Developer

Building web agency with ReactJS, Typescript, Styled Components and Vite. Added APIs with Express and GraphQL.

2023

GrupoR5

Front End Developer

Building user interfaces and user experience of web components with ReactJS, Typescript, Styled Components.

2020 - 2023

Inxeption

Front End Developer

Feature development and bug fixing. Agile scrum methodology. HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, TypeScript, Sass, GraphQL.

2019 - 2020

Inaltect S.A.S.

Software Analyst

Developed and maintained mobile bank app in React, TypeScript, Redux - Sagas.

2017 - 2019

Freelancer

Fullstack Developer

Development of SPA with NextJS, MongoDB, ExpressJS, Restful Api. Portfolio links in linked in profile.

2014 - 2017

GHR South America S.AS.

Systems Engineer

Support T-Systems internal app, and system admin.

2012 - 2013

Oralaser Clínica las Vegas

Systems Engineer

Management, monitoring installed IT systems infrastructure.

LAN Admin: HP ProLiant G5, G6 Win Server 2008R2 – DC, AD, DNS, DHCP, security policies, antivirus console, wireless end user support.

Education

2010

Dutchess Community College

Information Management

Associates in Computer Science

2007

Beacon High School

Contact

- https://github.com/alejandroyunes
- https://stackoverflow.com/users/8133300/alejandro-yunes
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alejandro-yunes-bb562720a/